Shreeyanshi Gupta

Email: shrynshigupta06@gmail.com | Mobile: 7895900956 | LinkedIn

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

As a self-motivated web developer with 2+ years of experience in both **front-end and back-end development**, I am dedicated to continuously learning and enhancing my skills. I am actively seeking new opportunities that will enable me to leverage my technical skills, collaborate with like-minded individuals, and further my career goals.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, TypeScript, C, C++

Frameworks : Node.js, Angular

Databases : MongoDB, MySQL

Frontend Dev : HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Angular Material

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Nov 2020 – Present

DLT Labs

- Designed and developed dynamic and responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Tailwind, and Angular Material.
- Extensively worked on developing and integrating **REST APIs** and databases into the client-side applications.
- Collaborated with different teams on multiple products that provide a one-stop solution to blockchain enthusiasts.
- Actively participated in end-to-end product delivery, collaborating with cross-functional teams from initial
 planning and development to testing, debugging, and deployments..

Software Engineer Trainee

Feb 2020 – Oct 2020

Newgen Software

- Worked on a hybrid mobile application for the client.
- **Troubleshoot issues** and **fixed bugs** in the backend as well as integrate new functionalities to the existing application.

EDUCATION

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science

KIET Group Of Institutions Aug 2016 – Oct 2020

PROJECTS

Shopkart

- * Shopkart is an application which integrates our online and offline shopping experience through its website and mobile application.
- * Technologies Used: Node.js, MongoDB, React.js, Flutter
- * Team Project | Role: Backend Developer

DSC KIET Website

- * The website includes detailed information about the events (boot camps, hackathons, coding contests, etc) organized by the team for the community and opportunities (internships, meetups) for them.
- * Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

Campus Dost

- * A guide built for the college campus which includes all the relevant information for campus members.
- * Technologies Used: Node.js, MongoDB